Previously on Smallville.
You ran off with a girl you barely know and got married.
It wasn't legal.
I was on red kryptonite, Mom.
Jason, what's really going on here?
Where this is heading with us, I just don't think you're ready.
There's a part of me that never feels freer than when I'm with Alicia.
You know what she did.
She tried to kill Lana and she tried to kill you.
Alicia needs to be in an institution.
Why'd they let her out of Belle Reve?
It's a little something my doctor came up with.
Keeps me from using my powers.
Why did you just walk out on this relationship?
I think that my mother arranged it.
Well, you don't even see what you did was wrong.
You dosed me with red kryptonite!
Look, I know that we can never be together after what I did.
Whatever's going on, it doesn't change the way that I feel about you.
I love you, Clark.
For as long as I live, I'm never gonna reveal your secret.
I love rock and roll.
So stop taking time and dance with me.
So I'll be your dog and ask for his name.
You.
Right there.
Say it doesn't matter cause everything seems the same.
Yeah, I love you, guys.
I said we'll take you home.
So we can be alone.
That's where I'm moving on.
And here's with me.
Yeah, baby.
That's where I'm moving on.
And here's with me.
Yeah, baby.
Singing I love rock and roll.
So put another dime in the jib I made back.
I love rock and roll.
So come take your time and dance with me.
Woo!
First to marry the girl, now we stay together?
That was subtle, Lois.
It's good.
I think I've seen enough for one night.
Lana, wait.
I just want to apologize.
For what?
Trying to kill me or not succeeding?
Look, all I want is a chance.
To prove to you who I really am.
You already have.
I can't believe you brought her here.
Jason, listen.
Listen to what?
Another apology?
You think just cause she says she's better that everything's gonna be okay?
Come on, man.
I'm sorry.
I failed because I want what's best for me.
I knew you could get this.
I have him for you.
Oh.
I plan to see her again tomorrow morning.
I don't want anução with δια in my January BRL-73 little, but...
Good luck to Botticelli's girl, I dare to say.
Onda, that eder dul-be borne out Abbot-Jose and her father took one.
Did they both not have any work?
Yeah.
I see it, I see it.
Let we wait for Brunetti.
Whoa.
He's late as all right.
Hooray.
He seems really good.
I clearer do.
What?
Those two get married?
Thank you.
Lana?
Hey, can you hear me?
Lana.
Lana, look at me.
Somebody save me.
Don't care how you do it.
Just stay, stay.
Come on.
I've been waiting for you.
Just stay.
I've made this whole world.
I've done for you.
Just stay, stay.
Come on.
How's Lana?
Is she okay?
Hey, Clark, yeah, she's fine.
I mean, lucky for her,
Jason pulled a team.
T.J. Hooker and Brooke
are bathroom door down.
Only to discover
Lana's mystery assailant
had somehow flown the coop.
So, have they arrested
your arm ornament yet?
What?
Sheriff Adams was just here
and she spent a lot of time
focusing on the
attacked inside a locked room
scenario.
And the name Alicia Baker
came up more than once
in a bunny boiler kind of way.
Alicia didn't do this.
Ever since she was released
from Belle Reve,
she's been wearing
a lead bracelet.
It prevents her
from using her abilities.
And did she also happen
to be wearing anything
low-cut when she spun you
that tail?
Because I'm not sure
you're thinking with
your big brain here.
Clark, just because
Alicia says that the bracelet
keeps her from teleporting
doesn't mean that
it's the truth.
She was with me
when Lana got attacked.
I was saying goodnight
in Granville.
Yeah, but every second?
You have to admit
that she can transport
easier than Captain Kirk.
And she did try to carve
herself a Jack O'Lana
before, cut and dry.
Emphasis on the cut.
I'm telling you,
Alicia couldn't have done this.
I know her.
Clark.
Lana doesn't want to see you.
I'm getting a funny
sense of déjà vu here,
Mr. Kent.
Haven't we acted out
this particular charade before?
This is different, Sheriff.
If Alicia did not attack Lana,
she was with me.
I better not find out
you're covering for
that girlfriend of yours,
Mr. Kent.
Having you as an alibi
is the only thing
keeping me from tossing
her tail in jail.
Sheriff Adams already has
Alicia tried and convicted.
Sheriff Adams has a point, Clark.
First Las Vegas
and now an assault charge.
What are you doing?
What are you doing with this girl, Clark?
Alicia didn't do this.
Sonda, your girlfriend has problems
and this relationship is not healthy.
Why can't you see that?
You always told me to look
for the good in people,
to believe in them.
And Alicia deserves a second chance.
What I don't understand is
why do you continue to see her
knowing how we feel?
She kept my secret.
She got shot protecting me.
But what else does she have to do
to prove herself?
What if she did this, Clark?
What if she attacked Lana
the way she did before?
I'm not going to lie,
I'm not going to lie.
They're still together.
I'm going to go to bed.
Okay, bye, Alicia.
Bye.
Bye, Alex.
Have you ever thought
about getting out more?
This is coming from the hot shot
college student who ran away
from college this weekend.
It's Greek week.
So?
So, they're wearing their letters
on their shirts.
They sing group songs.
Oh.
The fraternities are having
a power pukey contest.
Oh, okay.
Enough said.
I don't understand why you came
out to Smallville though.
Well, believe it or not,
I like spending time
with you, little cousin.
meteors make freaks theory.
It's not just a theory, Lois.
Alicia Baker tried to kill my best friend twice,
and it was because of her meteor-induced abilities
that she was able to do that.
Did you know that Lana's bathroom door was locked?
Who else could have gotten in or out, for that matter?
That's what I want to know.
Chloe, we need to find out if there's anybody else in Smallville
who has abilities similar to Alicia's.
Clark, I'm sorry, but even if there was someone else like Alicia,
what would they have against Lana?
Hey, I finished that op-ed piece, Chloe.
Great.
Hey, Lois.
Hey.
I had a feeling I'd bump into you here.
I was wondering if you'd like to maybe have a cup of coffee
or something with me, maybe.
Coffee?
You know, Lois was just saying she needs to get out more.
I, I, look...
Excellent. It's a date.
Smallville's Glory Days.
Sounds interesting.
I think it is.
And I'll tell you about it over coffee.
Hey, Tim, uh, you were at the townland last night.
Did you see anything suspicious?
Um, no, nothing out of the ordinary.
But your mother, she was there, she was cleaning up,
and the blonde girl that you were with was in the alley.
Maybe they saw something.
Huh.
You look like a big cat in a small cage.
You all right?
No.
Someone saw a blonde girl in the alley behind the town
when Lana was attacked.
And somebody saw another blonde girl in the alley
because it wasn't me.
There's bound to be suspicion, Clark.
People think I did it.
Besides, you couldn't have done it because you were with me.
And you were wearing your bracelet.
Clark.
You lied to me.
I didn't lie, Dee.
I didn't think that I needed it.
You don't understand.
I couldn't give up my powers.
Again, it was worse than being in prison.
What would you do if somebody told you
that you couldn't use your abilities?
I don't know.
But I would give them away in a second
before I'd use them to hurt someone.
Yeah, so would I.
I'd better know, Clark.
You know that.
I just want people to accept me for who I am.
I think if you're honest with yourself,
they'll realize that deep down inside,
you want that, too.
Look, I'm so sorry
that I didn't tell you about the bracelet.
But I didn't do anything to hurt Lana.
I swear.
Jason, don't be ridiculous.
I'll be fine for a few hours.
You do realize that you were attacked in your own apartment,
behind a locked door.
You want me just to leave you alone
and spend the evening digging through the university's microfiche?
No.
Well, I'm not gonna let you flunk history.
Mom, ready to go?
Why don't Clark and I stay with Lana?
I think that that is a great idea.
Go.
I'll be fine.
All right.
Thanks.
I won't be long.
I'll be fine.
Mom, what are you doing here?
I had to come to make sure my son was all right.
I phoned Dr. Martin on the way here.
He can see you today.
I'm fine.
I've been hurt worse than football.
Well, it never hurts to get a second opinion from a real doctor.
Let it go, Mom.
It's just hard to see you suffering here by yourself.
You'd at least think your girlfriend would be here.
You really want to play that game?
This is not a game, Jason.
This is your life.
And I'm worried about the path you're heading down.
Oh, you mean the path you sent me down?
What are you talking about?
Lana?
The girl you made sure I met in Paris?
Are you serious?
I mean, how could anyone maneuver two people meeting and falling in love in Paris?
Mrs. Teague, I didn't know you were here.
Well, come in, Lana.
We were just talking about you.
Did Jason share his matchmaking theory with you?
Yeah, he did.
And what did you think?
That I had somehow used my mysterious powers to coerce you into going to Paris
at exactly the same time that my son was there?
You don't have to answer that.
I think she already has.
Lana, I'm not a perfect mother.
I can be overprotective and sometimes overprotective.
And I'm not a perfect mother.
I'm not a perfect mother.
Especially when it comes to the women in my son's life.
Mom?
I had nothing to do with getting the two of you together.
As you can probably realize from my reaction to it.
And why my son feels the need to blame me for meeting you
is something you should be asking yourself.
If you change your mind about the doctor, let me know.
Feel better.
Very good.
Thank you.
It won't work.
The one that they made me in Belle Reve was special.
It had to be able to release trace amounts of lead
into my bloodstream to dampen my abilities.
Remember?
I guess it's the thought that counts.
It's a pretty ugly thought.
Where were you last night?
I was wondering if you were ever going to call me again. Why?
Lana's boyfriend was attacked.
I was the one who saved him, and I found this in his car.
Okay, I didn't do it, Clark.
I don't know how that got there, but I...
It wasn't me.
Lucia, you have to turn yourself in.
You don't believe me.
I want to.
I really do.
But I need to stop who's doing this.
Okay, well, then find out who really did it.
Everybody thinks it's you.
Why, because of my powers?
Because I'm a freak?
You know what, Clark?
Maybe if everybody knew your secret, you'd be a suspect, too.
No, Lucia, this is not about your abilities.
It's really easy for you to say, Clark.
Everybody thinks that you're normal.
How do you think your friends would react
if they found out that you were exactly like me?
Well, just go to the office.
Go to the sheriff. We'll tell her what happened.
We'll explain everything.
She'll understand it, and it'll all work out.
Just explain it to her.
All right, I'll go with you.
If you tell her about your powers, too.
I can't do that.
Why not, Clark?
Don't you understand that
once people...
know the truth about us,
then they'll have to accept us for who we really are?
I'm sorry.
Yeah, I'm sorry, too.
Letting people know about us
is the only way that we're ever gonna be free, Clark.
Don't hate me for wanting that.
Goodbye, Clark.
Bye.
How's everything?
I did a friend of yours said he would?
And you won't say-
I mean, it's not just me.
Look, you lock her up on your desk
and you shut her up on the computer.
It it's not just me.
Yeah, it happens.
You do it, then everything breaks, doesn't it?
Yeah, I know.
You have a good friend,いい haben sie?
I know how you like friends,
and I expect that thing of yours
and that you like school aside,
but I do a lot more
And I trust you, Clark.
Superb, super helpful.
These kids' 11-year-olds
made me walk up the steps
and tell me when they're promote
the same thing.
Yeah, I feel it too.
You did.
Well, I heard her mom say
that latte machine down.
No, Sheriff, I came here to see you.
I found this in the car when Jason was attacked.
Belongs to Alicia.
You flip-flop more than a politician, Mr. Kent.
So now you think your girlfriend's guilty, huh?
Maybe.
Well, I hate to disappoint you, Mr. Kent,
but I've already been down that road.
Despite your claim that Ms. Baker was with you
at the time of the first incident,
I yanked her in for a little dog and pony.
Ms. Scarf may have been there, but your girlfriend wasn't.
Alicia Baker was locked in an interrogation room with me
at the time the second victim was attacked.
There's no way she could have done it.
No, her囉nhindi was awashing me in black.
I told driver Lee talking about the sister he'd been with for about 10 years.
So the director told him that she'd come to court
looking for alang tri umpire by calling her own number.
He squished my letter back and wrote me an old letter
saying counsel were offering to meetreliem of the
old newspaper.
A handkerchief.
I go, Ms. Baker.
Nurse genteel?
You write all these articles about the people you call freaks,
and you don't even realize that someone close to you is one of them.
Why are you ignoring what's right in front of your face, Chloe?
Don't you want to know the truth about Clark Kent?
Everyone knows you're crazy. Why should I believe you?
You don't have to. I'm going to prove it.
And then you can write the story of a lifetime.
A lifetime.
Where are we? What are you doing?
Giving you your next headline.
I'm making things better for Clark.
Clark, I'm on Old Wilson Road,
and there's something really wrong with the car. It won't stop.
Hang on!
Hurry!
Once you see this, you'll understand.
I know Clark can be who he really is.
And you can use that poison pen of yours to enlighten Smallville for a change.
Clark, what are you...
Don't worry, Chloe.
And you're not getting any better than me.
I'm going to take you to the restaurant.
To Ackley Village.
Ackley Village.
To the restaurant, trust me.
Where's Ackley?
If you know what I mean, go grab a привiy or maybe a little dessert.
Come.
Oh, my God!
Maybe you can come back.
Voila, Smallville, circa 1988.
Before the meteor shower.
After that, everything changed.
My father used to say that the meteor shower
infected Smallville somehow.
It brought an evil to our town.
Sounds like something from the sci-fi channel.
Yeah.
I'm sorry I get a little carried away by the past sometimes.
I don't have many memories of my father, you know.
He passed away when I was young.
I know what it's like to lose a parent.
My mom died when I was little.
I cherish the memories I have of her.
Yeah.
My favorites are when my father used to talk about Smallville
and the way things used to be.
I mean, look at it now.
Nobody cares about right or wrong or morality.
I mean, like that football coach dating a student.
It's not right.
They're both over 18.
Lois, it doesn't make it right.
No, I mean, rules.
Our rules are there for a reason.
If those two got away with it, then other people would try.
You see?
It's a good thing that they were punished.
So you think they were attacked,
because someone thought their relationship was immoral?
Um...
I think that they got exactly what they deserved.
Wow.
Just look at the time.
I've got to get back to the torch.
I have some studying to do.
I have to go to school.
Chloe, have you seen Clark?
What?
Have I seen Clark do what?
Uh...
Oh.
Yeah, I've seen him.
Where?
Why?
Did something happen?
Bad date.
I'm starting to think maybe Alicia isn't our resident psycho killer.
I need to find Clark.
He's probably zipping around looking for Alicia.
Are you all right?
Fine.
Yeah, fine.
Uh...
He's probably out at Alicia's house.
I'll swing by, see if he's there.
Can you give me a call if he shows up here?
Okay.
Glad you're finally home.
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm...
I'm just looking for evidence to leave at the next murder.
It was you.
No.
Everyone thinks that I'm guilty because of you.
You are guilty.
I mean, this really used to be such a nice little town.
You don't understand what you've done.
Even Clark thinks that I'm guilty.
I'm not kidding.
I already have.
I don't have any proof.
You certainly have grown.
I'm sorry.
Forgive me, but you'll have to refresh my memory, Mrs. Teague.
I won't let you go.
I wasn't aware that we'd met before.
No, please, Lex.
Call me Genevieve.
I served on numerous committees with your father
and your late mother.
I used to see you with them often.
A bored young boy at the opera, always getting into trouble.
Some of my finer moments, I'm sure.
Can I get you something, Genevieve?
I assure you, my tastes have matured.
I'm sure you've developed a taste for quite a lot of things, Lex.
I understand you have a relationship with Lana Lang.
Care to tell me where this is going?
My son is young.
Lex, young and headstrong, like that boy at the opera.
He can't always see what's best for him.
And you?
Yes, you can.
With the wisdom of age, yes, I can.
And what I see is that he's throwing his future away,
as is your friend.
Surely you know they're in a relationship that will never work.
I don't usually involve myself
in other people's affairs of the heart, Genevieve.
Did you intervene at the high school?
That was a civic matter.
Look, I'm not a family therapist,
but I would suggest that you talk to your son.
Oh, I've tried, Lex.
But as is often the way with young men,
they don't listen particularly to their mothers.
I was hoping I could persuade you to help me.
As I said, I don't interfere in other people's...
In other people's affairs of the heart, I know.
Perhaps you should look at the bigger picture, Lex.
Helping me could work to your advantage.
I recently came across some information
about how your father managed to overturn his conviction
and get out of prison.
Information you might find very interesting.
I'm sorry.
Alicia!
.
No, please no.
Please.
Alicia, no. No.
No!
Clark!
Oh, my God.
Clark, what happened?
I think I know who did this.
And where we can find him.
Hey, hey.
Even you thought she was guilty, didn't you?
Huh?
Yeah.
Try not to feel too bad.
I mean, hey, she did try to kill your girlfriend last year.
I tried to kill Lana. What does that make you?
No, try to understand, Clark.
I did what's right for Smallville.
I have to make things right.
You killed Alicia.
I loved her, and you took that away from me.
No.
You killed her!
Stop it!
Stop!
You killed her!
All she wanted was a chance.
You killed her.
Stop!
Stop, Clark.
Clark.
You're killing me.
Get off me and leave me alone.
Stop.
Clark.
You're killing him.
Stop.
Let him go.
He's gonna be okay.
Clark, he's gonna be okay.
I'm gonna be okay.
Now, why would Lex Luthor want to see me?
Let me take a stab at it.
Because you want to lecture me on the evils of a part-time coach dating an 18-year-old
high school student.
I took a hard line about the school rules, Jason, but that doesn't mean I don't appreciate
the individuals involved.
I'm sorry I cost you your job, and I'd like to make it up to you.
Really?
What do you mean?
You still haven't rescheduled my meeting with your HR guy over at Luther Corp.
I have a position you might find more appealing.
A position that pays $100,000 a year.
Because I'm obviously qualified for a $100,000 a year job.
My mother put you up to this, didn't she?
She's trying her best to get between Lana and me.
She's trying to do a lot more than that, Jason.
That's why I want to work together.
To find out what she's really up to.
You want to team up against my mother.
The enemy of my enemy.
And how do I know I can trust you?
You don't.
But what other choice do you have?
You don't know.
Clark.
Honey, you've been up here for two days.
What happened to Alicia...
It wasn't your fault.
I'd have believed her if she wouldn't be dead.
Clark, she was framed. There's...
There's no way you could have known that.
You could have trusted her.
Did you know that Alicia wanted me to go to the sheriff with her and tell her everything?
Alicia thought that if people knew the truth about me and what I can do,
they wouldn't be so quick to judge her.
But I didn't go.
I was too afraid of what people might think.
How they would react.
But what if she was right?
Because if people knew...
What I could do and who I really am...
Maybe she'd still be alive.
And I just can't forgive myself for that.
No, like you do.
You don't think I'll see her again.
I don't think so.
I think you'll definitely see her this time.
What?
I said I love you, Kaylee.
I don't love you, Kim.
You love me?
Camille, I love you.
Arnie?
Hello, you guys.
I just wanted to see you, videos are the best.
What's your name?
EMG.
Things we should have seen before blaming Alicia.
I think maybe I've seen too much already.
Spent the last four years ferreting out media freaks,
trying to expose them.
I never should have started this wall.
Chloe, you're a reporter.
You investigate and expose. That's who you are.
Yeah, well then I guess sometimes it sucks being me.
I'm sorry.
Lois, if you found out something,
something someone didn't want you to know about them,
would you tell them?
That depends. Is that person someone you care about?
Yeah.
And does keeping this secret hurt anyone?
No.
Then my answer is no.
If I really cared about that person,
I wouldn't tell them that I knew.
But I would go out of my way to be supportive of them
so that hopefully one day they would be comfortable enough
to tell me themselves.
No offence, Lois, but that's the last thing I expected to hear from you.
I've learned the hard way that people keep secrets for a reason.
Even from the people they're closest to.
Chloe, is there something you want to tell me?
Are you the one with the secret?
No.
No, it's not me.
Okay.
I'll see you in a couple of weeks or so.
Yeah.
I'm sure whoever it is that you're talking about
will tell you when they're ready.
Thanks.
Bye, baby.
Bye.
Safe drive home.
Okay.
Clark.
Why didn't you just tell me?
Thank you very much for making this possible.
Your npc is safe.
And-
Emily, I love you.
I can be awful.
Very good to hear.
Take me out
Far into the deeper water
Show me how, show me how
Hey, Clark.
I just wanted to say that I am so sorry
for everything.
It must have been so hard
being so different.
Having everyone judge you before they even know you.
Knowing that there's some people that
might never accept you.
I just...
I want you to know that I'm here for you.
If you ever need to talk.
Thanks, Chloe.
I appreciate that.
When I see you
Wild blue, wild blue
Wild blue
Wild, wild blue
Wild blue, wild blue
Wild blue
White Là H vide
White Là H vu
White Lù
Thank you.